yac.mx 2015-05-19

# Free download Virus Remover,Malware Removal,Antispyware, Antivirus tools for XP, Vista or Windows 7

## Privacy Policy

### ELEX'S STATEMENT OF PRIVACY PROTECTION

Elex attaches great importance to protecting your privacy. Before using the services or programs provided by Elex, please read carefully the following statements.

In order to provide more accurate and well-targeted services, Elex may use personal information submitted by you in the manners mentioned below; nevertheless, Elex will treat such information with a high level duty of diligence. Without your permission, Elex will not disclose such information or provide such information to any third party.

### Protecting YOUR Privacy

It is Elex's principle to respect the privacy of the personal information of our users. Elex will take reasonable measures to protect user's personal information, without disclosing such information to any third party other than its Partners (without the consent of the user), unless such disclosure is (i) required by law, court order or competent government departments or (ii) agreed to by the user. Exceptions will be applied if the user selects to accept such disclosures during the registration process (where applicable), or is otherwise stipulated on the disclosure or use of a user's personal information between the user and Elex and its Partners. The user shall bear any risks that may arise from any authorized disclosure of a user's personal information. For the operation and improvement of Elex's technologies and services, Elex may collect and use the non-personal information of its users, or provide such information to third parties, in order to provide better user experience and improve the quality of our services.

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

### Collection of Information

Elex may collect your personal information when you voluntarily opt to use our services, programs or provide us with your personal information. We may use your personal information to communicate with you, and may send certain mandatory service communications to you, such as notification, information on technical service issues, and security announcements. We may also occasionally send you product surveys or promotional mailings to inform you of other products or services available from Elex and its affiliates. Your download, installation and use of the software shall be deemed to constitute consent to our use of your personal information.  
Elex will provide a user to whom PII pertains with notice and obtain his or her affirmative consent prior to the merger of PII with pseudonymous information previously collected through the software for use in Online Preference Marketing.

The users' PII will not be supplemented with information from other sources.

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or mailing address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

The information obtained and collected by YAC includes Pseudonymous and PII information such as IP address, computer name, YAC cookies details, Product ID and contact details when replying to messages and emails.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you).
  * To process transactions   
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

www.yac.mx shows advertisements and 3-rd party content which might use cookies. This includes, but is not limited to: Google adsense advertising network, Add this content sharing platform, Affiliate networks: Revenuewire.com, OneNetworkDirect.com, cj.com, linkshare.com, cleverbridge.com and others. Cookies are collected to identify visitor arrival source or provide customized browsing experience. www.pcrisk.com is not responsible for the information they collect.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Possible uninstall remnants

After installing YAC software, alone or as part of a bundle, may leave tracking assets such as cookies, files, or registry entries that are referenced or active after uninstallation, by the participant or other 3rd parties.

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

In the event you submit feedback to us via our website, http://www.yac.mx/ we may collect and use certain of personal information you provide to us, including your e-mail address, which we may use to operate and improve our website and product(s)] and deliver the service or carry out improvements you have requested. These uses may include providing you with more effective customer service; making the sites, products or services easier to use. Please note that your feedback information will only be collected and used as reference by Elex.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.   
However, in case of material change on the Privacy Policy, Elex will inform you of related changes through mail, announce on the website, prompt of the software or other methods in advance.
